goldbamboo.com 2005-12-31

# GoldBamboo.com: privacy

August 5, 2004 

## General

GoldBamboo recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information we may collect from our on-line visitors. To this end, we are committed to using our best efforts to respect the privacy of our on-line visitors. It is our intent to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information received from and about you with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The following is the way we handle information learned about you from your visit to our website.

GoldBamboo strives to develop innovative services to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use Our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it

## Collective Data 

GoldBamboo may deposit certain bits of information called "cookies" in a visitor's computer. Cookies are sent back only to the web site that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site. Cookies can tell us how and when pages in a website are visited and by how many people. This technology does not collect personal identifiable information; the information collected is in an aggregate, non-identifiable form. With the information we can learn through this technology, we hope to improve our sites. 

## Cookies

GoldBamboo uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to provide content based on certain criteria. Additionally we track usage statistics to better understand how people interact with the site. Upon loading Gold Bamboo a session cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser to our servers. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. 

## Personally Identifiable Information 

At this time GoldBamboo collects no personally identifiable information. In the future personal information such as names, addresses, E-mail addresses and the like may be required to allow enhanced capabilities on the site. This information will be stored only when voluntarily provided by a website visitor.

## Links to Other Sites 

As a resource to our visitors, GoldBanboo provides links to other websites. We try to carefully choose websites which we believe are useful and meet our high standards. However, because websites can change so quickly, we can't guarantee the standards of every website link we provide or be responsible for the content of non-GoldBamboo sites. 

  * The sites displayed as search results or linked to by GoldBamboo's services are developed by people over whom GoldBamboo exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. 
  * GoldBamboo may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of GoldBamboo's search technology. For instance, this data helps us determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results. 

## Children

We do not specifically collect information about children. While health and wellness topics related to children are covered under the GoldBamboo site it is intended for research conducted by an adults. 

## Information sharing

  * We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. 
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which GoldBamboo or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country. 
  * In the event of a transfer of ownership of GoldBamboo, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * We may share aggregated information with others. Examples of this include the number of users who searched for "Anxiety" or how many users clicked on a particular sponsored link. 

## Changes to this Policy

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view. If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at privacymatters@GoldBamboo.com
